=Born Again=
=Episode 2=
(Two Hours Before the Wedding)
(This is...)
(Why am I back again?)
(Why?)
(Why is that?)
(This is the third time.)
What is going on?
He...
Gu Xiaotang.
Stay put in the next loop.
I'll come to you.
(How does he know about the loop?)
Who is he?
- Happy...
- Move!
Hello, police?
I'm stuck in the loop.
- Loop?
- Xiaotang.
Xiaotang, you can't file
a false police report.
Is it hypoglycemia again?
Are you hallucinating?
How about I go get you some sugar?
(Sign-in)
This is the wedding cake.
(Everyone knows
I'm allergic to peanuts.)
(Why were there peanuts in the cake?)
Xiaotang, where are you going?
Director Li,
you like to spice things up?
Let me spice you up.
Is it enough?
You knew I'm allergic to peanuts,
yet you put it in the cake.
Are you trying to kill me?
Kill you?
Xiaotang, I'm just helping you.
An influencer's wedding
can't be without a little drama.
Die!
A tiny bit of peanut powder
can kill you?
I find it hard to believe.
(Oh no.)
How about I test it out?
(Is everything)
(gonna start over again?)
Don't move.
♪The face deep in the heart♪
♪Suddenly clear and hazy♪
♪Across time and space, eyes meet again♪
♪Deeply trapped in the vortex♪
♪Searching for familiar outlines♪
Who are you?
How dare you meddle in here?
Watch out!
It's okay, you're safe now.
Get lost.
What's going on?
Who's this guy?
Didn't I tell you
to stay put
and wait for me?
I'll get you out of here.
The wound on the left hasn't healed.
Don't do strenuous activity.
(How does he know about my wound?)
Here.
You have hypoglycemia, right?
H-How did you know?
I don't know you. Who are you?
That's not important.
What's important is,
like you, I'm also trapped in today.
This is already the third loop,
right?
How do you know all this?
You can't go back,
or you'll enter the loop again.
Come with me. We can...
Why should I trust you?
In this world,
there's no one I can trust anymore.
And I didn't get
my contract termination fee.
I'm one step away from freedom.
I'm not going with you.
It's useless.
Unless you break the loop,
you'll never get that money.
Miss Gu, the wedding is about to start.
Where are you going?
Gu Xiaotang,
I've paid you.
Give me the negatives.
Get lost. I don't have time for you.
Gu Xiaotang, you can't leave.
What's going on?
Mom.
Xiaotang,
I apologize on his behalf.
We can cancel the wedding,
but
can you give
these photos to me?
If these photos get out,
Lu Group's stock price will plummet,
and thousands of employees
will be affected.
They are all innocent.
Is watching drama
really that entertaining?
You'll receive the compensation
you deserve.
But Xiaotang,
I would like
to borrow something else from you.
What are you doing? Let go of me!
- Let go of me!
- Move!
What...
What is this?
Xiaotang,
don't be afraid.
It will end soon.
What do you mean?
Xiaotang,
we need one of your kidneys.
You...
This is illegal.
- Let go of me!
- Illegal?
Xiaotang,
did you forget?
After the premarital health checkup,
out of your love for Qingyuan
and filial piety toward me,
you voluntarily signed
the organ donation consent form.
You forced me to sign that.
Xiaotang,
saving your mother-in-law
is only right and proper.
I will remember your kindness.
Mom, let's go.
To the outside world,
you just suddenly fell ill
and passed away
despite emergency treatment.
Look, this is good for everyone.
Do it.
Mr. Lu,
the anesthesia hasn't taken effect yet,
and she's still conscious.
This...
Watching herself being cut open,
isn't that more interesting?
What's going on?
- Why are the lights out?
- Turn them on!
Mr. Lu, something's wrong!
The power is out on this floor.
- Any backup generator?
- I don't know.
Darn it.
Where's the maintenance team?
Mr. Lu, something's wrong!
The power suddenly went out.
The scalpel...
We accidentally injured Mrs. Lu.
She's bleeding out
and her condition is critical.
Mom. Hurry!
Save my mom first!
Where's my mom? Where is she?
In that operating room.
Who are you?
Stop him!
Gu Xiaotang.
- You...
- My...
My name is Ye Shen.
Ye Shen?
Don't be afraid.
I'll get you out of here.
(Please wait outside the operating room)
Ye Shen.
(Countdown to Death)
I'm so sleepy.
Go to sleep.
I'll always stay by your side.
Ye Shen.
(Two Hours Before the Wedding)
♪The face deep in the heart♪
♪Suddenly clear and hazy♪
♪Across time and space, eyes meet again♪
♪Deeply trapped in the vortex♪
♪Searching for familiar outlines♪
♪Persistently guarding,
endlessly cycling♪
♪Even for just a second♪
♪If raindrops flow backward
into the sky♪
♪And sunlight reverses♪
♪As the sun rises and sets,
we reunite with yesterday♪
♪I'll build a dream with you♪
♪Upon the ruins, spring breeze arrives♪
♪Even if there's no end,
I won't regret the start♪
♪Eternity like a day, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to recognize my eyes♪
♪Following the tracks
of the days that were♪
♪A day like a lifetime, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to remember my name♪
♪I'll be the dawn you haven't seen♪